Guide to the Athletics and Recreation Department records, 1890-2009 RG0054
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Colonials Sports News, 1968-2004; RG0054 Series 22; 3.0 Linear feet (Box 4, Box 1, Box 2, Box 3)
  - GW Sports Communications press releases, 03/2003 (Box 4, Folder 129)
  - GW Sports Communications press releases, 04/2003 (Box 4, Folder 130)
  - GW Sports Communications press releases, 05/2003 (Box 4, Folder 131)
  - GW Sports Communications press releases, 06/2003 (Box 4, Folder 132)
  - GW Sports Communications press releases, 07/2003 (Box 4, Folder 133)
  - GW Sports Communications press releases, 08/2003 (Box 4, Folder 134)
  - GW Sports Communications press releases, 09/2003 (Box 4, Folder 135)
  - GW Athletics Communications press releases, 10/2003 (Box 4, Folder 136)
  - GW Athletics Communications press releases, 11/2003 (Box 4, Folder 137)
  - GW Athletics Communications press releases, 12/2003 (Box 4, Folder 138)
  - GW Athletics Communications press releases, 01/2004 (Box 4, Folder 139)
  - GW Athletics Communications press releases, 02/2004 (Box 4, Folder 140)
  - GW Athletics Communications press releases, 03/2004 (Box 4, Folder 141)
  - GW Athletics Communications press releases, 04/2004 (Box 4, Folder 142)
  - GW Athletics Communications press releases, 05/2004 (Box 4, Folder 143)
- Intramural sports handbooks, 1950-1986; RG0054 Series 23; 0.5 Linear foot (Box 1)
  This series consists of intramural sports handbooks. The materials range in date from 1950-86.
  Formerly ACC#922, formerly RG6.4
  - Intramural Sports Handbooks, 1950-1951 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Intramural Sports Handbooks, 1953-1954 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Intramural Sports Handbooks, 1954-1955 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Intramural Sports Handbooks, 1955-1956 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Intramural Sports Handbooks, 1956-1957 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Intramural Sports Handbooks, 1957-1958 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Intramural Sports Handbooks, 1958-1959 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Intramural Sports Handbooks, 1959-1960 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Intramural Sports Handbooks, 1960-1961 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Intramural Sports Handbooks, 1961-1962 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Intramural Sports Handbooks, 1962-1963 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Intramural Sports Handbooks, 1963-1964 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Intramural Sports Handbooks, 1964-1965 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Intramural Sports Handbooks, 1965-1966 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Intramural Sports Handbooks, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Intramural Sports Handbooks, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Intramural Sports Handbooks, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Intramural Sports Handbooks, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Intramural Sports Handbooks, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Intramural Sports Handbooks, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Intramural Sports Handbooks, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Intramural Sports Handbooks, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Colonial Cager newspaper, 1973-1981; RG0054 Series 24; 1 Linear foot (Box 1)
  This series consists of the Colonial Cager newspaper of the basketball team. The materials range in date from 1973-81.
  Formerly ACC#923, RG6.4
  - Colonial Cager, 12/10/1973 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    loose
  - Colonial Cager, 12/06/1975 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Colonial Cager [1/2], 11/30/1976 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Colonial Cager [2/2], 11/30/1976 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    in paper
  - Colonial Cager [1/2], 11/28/1977 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Colonial Cager [2/2], 11/28/1977 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Colonial Cager, 01/14/1978 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Colonial Cager, 11/28/1978 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Colonial Cager, 11/28/1978 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Colonial Cager, 12/02/1978 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Colonial Cager, 12/05/1978 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Colonial Cager, 12/22/1978 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Colonial Cager, 01/13/1979 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Colonial Cager, 01/17/1979 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Colonial Cager, 01/25/1979 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Colonial Cager, 02/03/1979 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Colonial Cager, 02/07/1979 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Colonial Cager, 02/10/1979 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Colonial Cager, 02/24/1979 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Colonial Cager, 11/30/1981 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Colonial Cager - extra copies vol. 5, #1, undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Colonial Cager - extra copies vol. 6, #1, undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Colonial Cager - extra copies vol. 7, #1, undated (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Colonial Cager - extra copies vol. 10, #1, undated (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Athletic uniforms and George mascot costume, 1980-1989; RG0054 Series 26; 1 Linear foot (Box 1)
  This series consists of old basketball, baseball, and soccer uniforms; and George mascot costume. The materials range in date from 1980-89.
  Formerly ACC#929, formerly RG6.4
- Athletic uniforms and artifacts, 1935-2009; RG0054 Series 27; 3.5 Linear feet; 3 boxes, and 1 oversize textile box. (Box 2, Box 1, Box 3)
  This series consists of a football from 1946 game, Colonials license plate frames, basketball letterman sweater of John Holup (1954), basketball jerseys of Peter Young (c.1990), practice basketball jerseys, t-shirts (water polo, alumni basketball game), GW letters for jackets, GW embroidered seals, letterman sweater of Lewis Carroll (1935), football uniform, and football program. The materials range in date from 1935-94. (Formerly ACC#1047, RG6.4)
  This series also contains 1 varsity letterman's jacket and 13 athletic uniforms from the 1990s to the late 2000s. Athletics represented: soccer, golf, baseball, men's basketball, and women's basketball.
  - Letterman sweater of John Holup, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Basketball jerseys - home and away game jerseys of Peter Young #32, 1987-1990 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Basketball practice jersey #33, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Basketball practice jersey #25, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Tee-shirt - "Colonials Why You Came to the Game" (given out to fans), undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Tee shirt - GW Water Polo, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Tee-shirt - "Colonials Alumni Basketball game", undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Tea towel with "Colonials" from the General Alumni Association, undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Two embroidered emblems of the GW seal, undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Two "GW" letters for lettermen jackets, undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Football belonging to Peter P. Labukus 1946 game vs. Citadel (18-0) (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Plaque - J.B. Martin Memorial Scholarship Award given to Peter Lubukus, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Two license plate frames "GWU Colonials", undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Tea towel from Student Association - Homecoming, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Letterman's sweater of Lewis Carroll, 1935 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Buff colored sweater with "GW" letter bordered in blue
  - Football jersey, 1935 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    #44 in blue lettering on buff. Front has vertical red strips, back is blue with buff and red stripes. Also with it are leggings.
  - Football program, 10/05/1935 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    GW vs. Alabama game at Griffith Stadium. Also includes news clippings noting attendence of 27,000 for the game and featuring Lewis Carroll.
  - Varsity letterman's jacket, circa 1990s; Series 27; 1 artifact(s) (Box SERIES 27 BOX 4, Object 1)
  - Soccer game jersey, circa late 1990s; Series 27; 1 artifact(s) (Box SERIES 27 BOX 4, Object 2)
  - Soccer game jersey, circa late 1990s; Series 27; 1 artifact(s) (Box SERIES 27 BOX 4, Object 3)
  - Soccer game jersey, circa late 1990s; Series 27; 1 artifact(s) (Box SERIES 27 BOX 4, Object 4)
  - Golf team pants, circa early 1990s; Series 27; 1 artifact(s) (Box SERIES 27 BOX 4, Object 5)
  - Baseball game jersey pinstripe with script Colonials, circa early 2000s; Series 27; 1 artifact(s) (Box SERIES 27 BOX 4, Object 6)
  - Men's basketball shooting shirt No. 21, 2008-2009; Series 27; 1 artifact(s) (Box SERIES 27 BOX 4, Object 7)
  - Men's basketball warm-up pants (snap-off), circa 2000s; Series 27; 1 artifact(s) (Box SERIES 27 BOX 4, Object 8)
  - Baseball blue mesh batting practice jersey with gold GW, circa 2000s; Series 27; 1 artifact(s) (Box SERIES 27 BOX 4, Object 9)
  - Men's basketball blue game jersey No. 11 (Cheyenne Moore), 2005-2007; Series 27; 1 artifact(s) (Box SERIES 27 BOX 4, Object 10)
  - Women's basketball game jersey No. 31 (Greba Outen Barlow), 2001-2002; Series 27; 1 artifact(s) (Box SERIES 27 BOX 4, Object 11)
  - Women's basketball white game shorts, circa early 2000s; Series 27; 1 artifact(s) (Box SERIES 27 BOX 4, Object 12)
  - Women's basketball gold shooting shirt, circa early 2000s; Series 27; 1 artifact(s) (Box SERIES 27 BOX 4, Object 13)
  - Women's basketball warm-up jacket snap-up (white), circa early 2000s; Series 27; 1 artifact(s) (Box SERIES 27 BOX 4, Object 14)
  - Women's basketball warm-up jacket snap-up (blue), circa early 2000s; Series 27; 1 artifact(s) (Box SERIES 27 BOX 4, Object 15)
  - Crew team sweatpants, 1963 (Box 5, Object 1)
- Blanket, sweater, and jersey, 1954; RG0054 Series 28; 1 Linear foot (Box 1)
  This series consists of a blanket with George Washington letter, letterman sweater, and practice jersey #34 from football team from 1954.
  Formerly ACC#1059, RG6.4
  - Blanket with GW Letter, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Letterman Sweater, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Practice Football Jersey (#34), 1954 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Sports media guides, 1978-2006; RG0054 Series 29; 1.5 Linear feet (Box 4, Box 5, Box 1, Box 2, Box 3)
  This series consists of sports media guides to crew, baseball, soccer, and volleyball. The materials range in date from 1978-2004.
  Formerly ACC#138, formerly RG6.4
  - Fall Sports Schedule, 1991-2003 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Does not include schedules from 1992 and 1994
  - Winter/Spring Sports Schedule, 1990-2003 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Does not include schedules from 1991, 1993, and 1995
  - All-Sports Media Guide, 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - All-Sports Media Guide, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - All-Sports Media Guide, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Item missing
  - Baseball and Post Season Guides, 1978-2004 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Post Season Guide only available for 1998
  - Crew, 1996-2004 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Incudes guide for Crew Classic
  - Cross Country, 1991-2003 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Guides for 1992-1994 not available
  - Golf, 1996-2004 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Gymnastics, 1989-2004 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Guides for 1990, 1992-1995, 1997, and 2002 not available
  - Women's Lacrosse, 2002-2004 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Rowing, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Squash, 2002-2004 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Men's Soccer, 2002-2003 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Men's Soccer, 1983- 2001 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Guides for 1986 and 1992-1994 not included
  - Women's Soccer, 1995-2003 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Softball, 2003-2004 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Swimming and Diving, 1990-2003 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    Guides for 1993-1994 not available
  - Men's Tennis, 1991-2004 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    Guides for 1993-1997 not available
  - Volleyball, 20002003 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Volleyball, 1989-1999 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Guides for 1990, 1992-1994, and 1996 not available
  - Women's Tennis, 1996-2004 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Water Polo, Men's, 1989-2003 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    Guides for 1990-1994, 1996, and 2001-2002 not available
  - Water Polo, Women's, 2001-2004 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Baseball, 2005-2006 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Cross Country, 2004-2005 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Golf, 2004-2006 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Gymnastics, 2005-2006 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Lacrosse, 2006 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Rowing and Crew, 2005-2006 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Men's Soccer, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Women's Soccer, 2004-2005 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Softball, 2005-2006 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Squash, 2004-2006 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Swimming and Diving, 2004-2006 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Tennis, Men's, 2005-2006 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Tennis, Women's, 2005-2006 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Volleyball, 2004-2005 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Water Polo, Men's, 2004-2005 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Water Polo, Women's, 2005-2006 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Football programs, 1930-1966; RG0054 Series 30; 3.5 Linear feet (Box 1, Box 7, Box 9, Box 10, Box 6, Box 8, Box 4, Box 5, Box 2, Box 3)
  This series contains football programs listing the rosters and includes photographs and statistics. The material ranges in date from 1930-66.
  Formerly ACC#366; formerly RG6.4
  - South Dakota vs. GW, 10/17/1930 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - GW vs. Elon, 10/03/1931 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Tulsa vs. GW, 10/16/1931 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Alabama vs. GW, CUA vs. Georgetown, 12/12/1931 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Alabama vs. GW, 10/08/1932 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Iowa vs. GW, 10/28/1932 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - North Dakota State vs. GW, 11/04/1932 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - William and Mary vs. GW, 11/11/1932 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Oklahoma vs. GW, 11/24/1932 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Cover missing
  - Auburn vs. GW, 10/21/1933 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - West Virginia Wesleyan vs. GW, 10/27/1933 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Tennessee vs. GW, 11/04/1933 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Washington & Jefferson vs. GW, 11/10/1933 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Kansas vs. GW, 12/02/1933 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Citadel vs. GW, 10/12/1934 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Wake Forest vs. GW, 10/26/1934 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Vanderbilt vs. GW, 11/03/1934 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Louisiana State vs. GW, 11/10/1934 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - North Dakota vs. GW, 11/23/1934 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Oklahoma vs. GW, 11/29/1934 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Alabama vs. GW, 10/05/1935 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Rice vs. GW, 11/02/1935 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Davis-Elkins vs. GW, 11/08/1935 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Tulsa vs. GW, 11/15/1935 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - North Dakota vs. GW, 11/28/1935 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Mississippi vs. GW, 10/09/1936 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Arkansas vs. GW, 10/16/1936 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Wake Forest vs. GW, 10/23/1936 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Davis-Elkins vs. GW, 11/07/1936 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - West Virginia vs. GW, 11/26/1936 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Wake Forest vs. GW, 10/01/1937 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - West Virginia Wesleyan vs. GW, 10/08/1937 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Alabama vs. GW, 10/23/1937 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Tulsa vs. GW, 10/29/1937 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Mississippi vs. GW, 11/05/1937 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - North Dakota State vs. GW, 11/13/1937 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Furman vs. GW, 09/30/1938 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Butler vs. GW, 10/07/1938 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Colorado vs. GW, 10/15/1938 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Davis-Elkins vs. GW, 10/21/1938 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Mississippi vs. GW, 10/28/1938 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Clemson vs. GW, 11/05/1938 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Kansas vs. GW, 11/12/1938 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Bucknell vs. GW, 11/19/1938 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - West Virginia vs. GW, 11/24/1938 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Davis-Elkins vs. GW, 10/07/1939 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Butler vs. GW, 10/14/1939 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - The Citadel vs. GWU, 10/20/1939 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Georgetown vs. GW, 10/28/1939 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Clemson vs. GW, 11/03/1939 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Kansas vs. GW, 11/18/1939 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Bucknell vs. GW, 11/25/1939 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - GW vs. Kentucky, 10/19/1940 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - West Virginia vs. GW, 10/25/1940 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Wake Forest vs. GW, 11/01/1940 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Bucknell vs. GW, 11/09/1940 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Kansas vs. GW, 11/16/1940 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Georgetown vs. GW, 11/23/1940 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Mount St. Mary's vs. GW, 09/27/1941 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Manhattan College vs. GW, 10/03/1941 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Washington& Lee vs. GWU, 10/10/1941 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Georgetown vs. GWU, 10/17/1941 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - William and Mary vs. GW, 10/24/1941 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Clemson vs. GW, 10/31/1941 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Furman vs. GW, 11/08/1941 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Bucknell vs. GW, 11/14/1941 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Wake Forest vs. GW, 11/20/1941 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Richmond vs. GW, 10/03/1942 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Furman vs. GW, 10/16/1942 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Kentucky vs. GW, 10/30/1942 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Wake Forest vs. GW, 11/13/1942 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Wayne vs. GW, 10/19/1946 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    Original and photocopy
  - William and Mary vs. GW, 11/16/1946 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - GW vs. Virginia, 09/27/1947 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - GW vs. VMI, 10/04/1947 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - GW vs. Wash. and Lee, 10/11/1947 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Miami vs. GW, 10/24/1947 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Virginia Tech vs. GWU, 10/31/1947 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Georgetown vs. GW, 11/22/1947 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - GW vs. Kingspoint, 11/27/1947 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - VMI vs. GW, 10/02/1948 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    2 copies: one original, one reproduction
  - Kansas vs, GW, 10/15/1948 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Maryland vs. GW, 10/23/1948 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Washington and Lee vs. GW, 10/21/1949 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Duke vs. GW, 11/21/1949 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - South Carolina vs. GW, 10/27/1950 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Maryland vs. GW, 11/07/1953 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    3 copies: 2 original, 1 photocopy
  - Richmond vs. GW, 11/30/1951 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    One original, one photocopy
  - Washington and Lee vs. GW, 10/05/1952 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - GW vs. VMI, 10/24/1952 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - North Carolina State vs. GW, 10/03/1953 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - GW vs. West Virginia, 10/16/1953 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Maryland vs. GW, 11/07/1953 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Richomond vs. GW, 11/21/1953 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - All-South Football Annual, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - GW vs. Wake Forest, 09/18/1954 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - VMI vs. GW, 09/25/1954 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - GW vs. Virginia, 10/02/1954 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - West Virginia vs. GW, 10/09/1954 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - GW vs. Pennsylvania, 10/16/1954 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - William and Mary vs. GW, 10/22/1954 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - VPI vs. GW, 11/05/1954 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Maryland vs. GW, 11/20/1954 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - GW vs. VMI, 09/24/1955 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Virginia vs. GW, 10/01/1955 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - GW vs. Florida, 10/08/1955 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Pennsylvania vs. GW, 10/15/1955 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - William and Mary vs. GW (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Virginia Tech vs. GW, 10/29/1955 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - GW vs. West Virginia, 11/04/1955 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - University of Richmond, 11/12/1955 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Maryland vs. GW, 11/19/1955 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - GW vs. Miami, 09/22/1956 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Furman vs. GW, 09/29/1956 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - GW vs. Hardin-Simmons, 10/05/1956 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - GW vs. Boston University, 10/13/1956 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - GW vs. VMI, 10/19/1956 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - GW vs. William and Mary, 10/26/1956 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - GW vs. West Virginia, 11/03/1956 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Richmond vd. GW, 11/09/1956 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - GW vs. Citadel, 11/17/1956 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - GW vs. Texas Western ( Sun Bowl game), 01/01/1957 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - William and Mary vs. GW, 09/21/1957 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - GW vs. Citadel, 09/27/1957 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - GW vs. Furman, 10/05/1957 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Air Force vs. GW, 10/11/1957 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    2 Original and photocopy
  - VMI vs. GW, 10/26/1957 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Boston University vs. GW, 11/01/1957 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Navy vs. GW, 11/16/1957 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Citadel vs. GW, 09/27/1958 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - GW vs. Furman, 10/03/1958 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - GW vs. Richmond, 10/17/1958 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - West Virginia vs. GW, 11/01/1958 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Navy vs. GW, 11/15/1958 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    Photocopy
  - Wichita University vs. GW, 11/22/1958 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Detroit vs. GW, 09/18/1959 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - West Virginia vs. GW, 10/02/1959 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Wichita University vs. GW, 10/09/1959 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - GW vs. Furman, 10/17/1959 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - William and Mary vs. GW, 10/24/1959 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - GW vs. Florida, 09/17/1960 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - GW vs. Citadel, 09/24/1960 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - William and Mary vs. GW, 10/01/1960 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - GW vs. VMI, 10/07/1960 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Boston University vs. GW, 10/15/1960 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Air Force Academy vs. GW, 10/29/1960 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - GW vs. Richmond, 11/04/1960 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - GW vs. Virginia Tech, 11/11/1960 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - West Virginia vs. GW, 11/19/1960 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Florida State vs. GW, 09/16/1961 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - GW vs. Citadel, 09/23/1961 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - GW vs. VMI, 10/07/1961 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    DC Stadium Dedication Program, 4 copies
  - Richmond vs. GW, 10/14/1961 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - GW vs. William and Mary, 10/20/1961 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - GW vs. Boston University, 10/27/1961 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - GW vs. West Virginia, 11/04/1961 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Virginia Tech vs. GW, 11/17/1961 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - VMI vs. GW, 09/15/1962 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - GW vs. Brigham Young, 09/29/1962 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - GW vs. Furman, 10/05/1962 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Boston University vs. GW, 10/13/1962 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - West Virginia vs. GW, 10/20/1962 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - GW vs. Army, 10/27/1962 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - GW vs. Richmond, 11/02/1962 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - VMI vs. GW, 09/21/1963 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Furman vs. GW, 09/28/1963 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - GW vs. Citadel, 10/04/1963 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - GW vs. Virginia Tech, 10/11/1963 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Villanova vs. GW, 10/19/1963 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - William and Mary vs. GW, 10/26/1963 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - GW vs. West Virginia, 11/02/1963 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - GW vs. Brigham Young, 11/09/1963 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Vanderbilt vs. GW, 11/23/1963 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Boston University vs. GW, 09/26/1964 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - GW vs. Furman, 10/02/1964 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - GW vs. Virginia Tech, 10/10/1964 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - GW vs. Vanderbilt, 10/17/1964 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - GW vs. William and Mary, 10/23/1964 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Cincinnati vs. GW, 10/31/1964 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - GW vs. West Virginia, 11/07/1964 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - GW vs. Villanova, 11/14/1964 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Citadel vs. GW, 11/21/1964 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Temple vs. GW, 09/18/1965 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - GW vs. Citadel, 09/25/1965 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - GW vs. VMI, 10/02/1965 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - GW vs. Virginia Tech, 10/09/1965 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Cincinnati vs. GW, 10/15/1965 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - GW vs. William and Mary, 10/23/1965 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Davidson vs. GW, 10/30/1965 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Furman vs. GW, 11/06/1965 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - West Virginia vs. GW, 11/20/1965 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Virginia Tech vs. GW, 09/24/1966 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - GW vs. William and Mary, 10/01/1966 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - GW vs. Citadel, 10/08/1966 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - East Carolina vs. GW, 10/15/1966 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - VMI vs. GW, 10/22/1966 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - GW vs. Furman, 10/29/1966 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Army vs. GW, 11/05/1966 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - West Virginia vs. GW, 11/12/1966 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Villanova vs. GW, 11/24/1966 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    6 copies
  - Bound football programs, 10/27/1933-12/09/1950 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Bound football programs, 10/03/1952-10/11/1953 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Bound football programs, 09/24/1960-10/20/1961 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Bound football programs, 10/05/1962-11/02/1962 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Bound football programs, 09/21/1963-11/07/1964 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Bound football programs, 09/18/1965-11/24/1966 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Basketball media guides, 1969-2006; RG0054 Series 31; 7.5 Linear feet (Box 11, Box 12, Box 9, Box 10, Box 13, Box 4, Box 3, Box 2, Box 1, Box 8, Box 7, Box 6, Box 5)
  This series consists of basketball media guides, programs, yearbooks of men's and women's teams, and four videotapes from sports information office.
  The materials range in date from 1969-2004.